<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhea Ayase</title>
    <description>Former game programmer with passionate opinions about the industry, Discord admin and active contributor to gaming &amp; dev communities. Currently wearing her RedHat, playing with the delicate C# letters in Linux.</description>
    <link>http://rhea-ayase.eu/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://rhea-ayase.eu/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 10:22:29 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 10:22:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is Rhea?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;  The name is Radka, but I’m known as Rhea Ayase on the interwebz. I’m that rare unicorn, a female programmer. And a gamer. I’m an active contributor not only to dev communities, but also to the gaming ones. &lt;em&gt;Grill on the web!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  I used to be a streamer with rather decent amount of viewers, but now I stream only casually while still trying to put up a video or two every month and actively maintaining several large gaming communities on Discord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  I began my career in game development, leaving my C++ code all over the Angry Birds, later on a little bit of C++ and Python in the World of Tanks engine, and a lot of C# in several other released titles and prototypes. I’m currently wearing my Red Hat though. As you could have guessed, I’m on the dotnet and Azure teams. I love C#, I find C++ a bit too slow to use, and dislike Python for its whitespace syntax… Hate me for it if you want &lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;p&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  I was familiar with Linux for a long time, and actively started using it somewhere around 2008. My first desktop distribution was Mandriva 2008, later it was Arch Linux and during university I switched to BackTrack, because I studied security and felt like I might as well play around a little bit out of the standard sandbox… As far as servers go my first server experience was with CentOS, then I went through ClearOS briefly, and ended up using unRAID on my home-server. It was an interesting project to set up all the things. After university I went more casual and after I sold my notebook I was left with only my Windows PC and the unRAID server for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  One day I managed to inspire the desolate white space with the delicate &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;C#&lt;/code&gt; letters of simplified artificial intelligence, also known as the &lt;a href=&quot;http://botwinder.info&quot;&gt;Botwinder&lt;/a&gt;. A little almost-open-source project, a Community Management bot for Discord. It was running on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/b4x64zhcthvu8jm/RPi_1.jpg&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt; in Raspbian Linux, however during the summer 2016 it became very popular and the poor tiny raspie was not enough anymore. And so we are running it from a strronk VPS now, together with its website. Nope, I’m not a web developer! My fiancé is responsible for that, it is Laravel somethingsomething. &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;p 
&lt;br /&gt;   Oh and I’m running Fedora 24 on my RedHat issue Lenovo notebook. &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://rhea-ayase.eu/img/RPi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Raspberry Pi 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 1990 04:07:19 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://rhea-ayase.eu/articles/1990-08/Who-is-Rhea</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rhea-ayase.eu/articles/1990-08/Who-is-Rhea</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
